Register to The Ernest Trow Carter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music by Carter, 1879-1968; Series I; 13.75' (33 boxes)
  - Opera and Stage Works, I.A
    - [White bird. German & English] The White Bird: Opera in one act / Music by Ernest Carter; Poem by Brian Hooker. -- c1924., 1 manuscript score (344 p.), bound; 42 cm. (Box 44)
      Holograph, signed, in ink and pencil
    - [White bird] The White Bird / Music by Ernest Carter; Poem by Brian Hooker., 1 manuscript score (335 sheets); 36 cm. (Box 15, Folder 114-118)
      Opera in one act
    - [White bird. German & English] The White Bird / Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1919-1927., 25 manuscript parts; 33 cm. (Box 15; 16, Folder 119-121; 122-126)
      Holographs, signed, and manuscript in ink with pencil additions
      Words by Brian Hooker
      Includes voice and orchestra parts
      Note on old wrapper concerning some parts: mended Jan. 21, 1941
    - [White bird. German & English] The White Bird / Music by Ernest Carter; Poem by Brian Hooker. -- ca. 1926-1927., 17 manuscript parts; 33 cm. (Box 17, Folder 127-130)
      Orchestral parts only
    - [White bird. German & English] ca. 1919-1939., 13 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 17, Folder 131)
      Holographs, signed, and manuscript, in part in Otto Fessler's hand in ink
      Miscellaneous voice and orchestra parts
    - [White bird. I am the glowing sky] The White Bird: 8-measure insert, first used in N.Y. production, Feb. 7/37., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 17, Folder 132)
    - [White bird. I am the glowing sky. Vocal score] The White Bird: Insert at page 17., 1 manuscript vocal score ([1] sheet); 28 cm. (Box 17, Folder 133)
      Negative photocopy laid in
    - [White bird. I am the glowing sky. Vocal score] The White Bird: Insert at page 17., 1 manuscript vocal score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 17, Folder 133)
    - [White bird. I am the glowing sky. Vocal score] White Bird., 1 manuscript vocal score ([1] sheet); 32 cm. (Box 17, Folder 133)
    - [White bird. I am the glowing sky. Vocal score] Aria from The White Bird: Opera in One Act / The Music by Ernest Carter; The Poem by Brian Hooker. -- 1941 Jun., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 17, Folder 133)
      Exhibit card laid in, with note: Exhibited in Los Angeles, 1941
    - [White bird. Libretto] The white bird: Opera in one Act / The Poem by Brian Hooker. -- 1916 Aug. 20., 68 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 134)
      On title page: Complete text, for the Composer; first revision, August 20, 1916
    - [White bird. Libretto] The white bird: Opera in One Act / The Music by Ernest Carter; The Poem by Brian Hooker. -- ca. 1924., 54 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 135)
      Note on title page: This copy was used + marked by Chas. T.H. Jones for the Chicago production of 1924, which he staged
    - [White bird. Libretto] The White Bird: opera in one act / The Poem by Brian Hooker; The Music by Ernest Carter. -- New Haven: Yale University Press, 1924., 66 p.; 21 cm. (Box 18, Folder 136)
      Two paperback copies with markings by Carter (one inscribed) and a hardcover copy
    - [White bird. Libretto] The white bird. -- ca. 1950., 18 parts; 16 x 23 cm. (Box 18, Folder 137)
      Individual vocal parts
      Note on old envelope: small type written booklets - separate parts of White Bird 1950
    - [White bird. Libretto] The white bird: Opera in One Act / The Music by Ernest Carter; The Poem by Brian Hooker., 54 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 138)
      Typescript with pencil markings by Carter
      Sketch for stage setting by Charles Curran taped to cover, pencil sketch for stage setting laid in
      Stamp with Mrs. Archibald Freer's name and address on front cover
    - [White bird. Libretto] The white bird: Opera in One Act / The Music by Ernest Carter; The Poem by Brian Hooker., 54 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 139)
      Sheet with pencil notes headed "Mistakes in 1st libretto" laid in
      Copy with pencil markings and two sketches for stage settings laid in
    - [White bird. Libretto. German] Der weiße Vogel: Oper in einem Akt / Dichtung von Brian Hooker; Musik von Ernest Carter; Ins Deutsche übertragen von Fritz Remond. -- Berlin-Charlottenburg: Bühnen-Verlag Trask & Matthias G.m.b.H., c1924., 31 p.; 15 cm. (Box 18, Folder 140)
      Two copies with "Osnabrück" cuts
    - [White bird. Libretto. German] Der weisse Vogel / Rohe deutsche Uebersetzung von M. McClaus. -- ca. 1926., 47 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 141)
      Typescript with markings
      Pencil note by Carter on first p.: Literal translation by Herrn M. McClaus - Original rec'd from him summer 1926, red ink by McClaus, pencil by E.T.C.
      Two copies laid in
    - [White bird. Libretto. German] Der weisse Vogel: Oper in einem Akt / Dichtung von Brian Hooker; Musik von Ernest Carter; Ins Deutsche übertragen von Fritz Remond. -- ca. 1927 Jan. 25., 34 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 142)
      Typescript with pencil and ink additions by Carter
      Two copies, note on cover of one copy: Rec'd back Jan 25/27
    - [White bird. Libretto. German] Der weisse Vogel: Rohe deutsche Uebersetzung / von M. McClaus. -- ca. 1929., 47 sheets; 29 cm. (Box 18, Folder 143)
      Pencil note by Carter on title page: copies by Mrs. Bader - summer of 1929
      Copy laid in
    - [White bird. Libretto. German] Der weisse Vogel: Oper in einem Akt / Dichtung von Brian Hooker; Musik von Ernest Carter; Ins Deutsche übertragen von Fritz Remond., 34 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 144)
      Business card belonging to M. MacClaus laid in
    - [White bird. Libretto. German] Der weisse Vogel., 7 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 18, Folder 145)
      Typescript (copy) with markings
      Note on first p.: Part of literal translation by Herrn M.McClaus
    - [White bird. Love duet; arr. Vocal score] The White Bird: Love Duet: (Transposition for Soprano and Tenor) / Ernest Carter. -- 1938 Dec. 17., 1 manuscript vocal score (13 p.); 33 cm. (Box 19, Folder 146)
      manuscript in ink with pencil additions
      Two positive photocopies with markings and a negative photocopy laid in
      Date appears at end of score
    - [White bird. Lullaby. Vocal score] Lullaby: from The White Bird / by Ernest Carter. -- 1924 May 11., 1 manuscript vocal score (6 p.); 35 cm. (Box 19, Folder 147)
      Date in lower left corner of first page
    - [White bird. Selections. German & English], [5] p. of music; 34 cm. (Box 19, Folder 148)
      Holograph in ink and pencil
      Themes and motives
    - [White bird. Selections], [1] sheet of music; 26 cm. (Box 19, Folder 148)
      Vocal part for the character "Warren"
    - [White bird. Selections. Vocal score] The White Bird: Recurring motives and themes / by Ernest Carter. -- 1925 Nov., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 19, Folder 149)
      manuscript in Otto Fessler's hand in ink
      Date from lower right corner of title page
    - [White bird. Selections. Vocal score] The White Bird: Recurring motives and themes / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 19, Folder 149)
    - [White bird. Selections. Vocal score], 1 manuscript vocal score ([2] sheets); 32 cm. (Box 19, Folder 149)
      Note on old envelope: Riverside material
    - [White bird (Sketches)], [2] sheets of music; 32 cm. (Box 19, Folder 150)
      Holographs in pencil
    - [White bird. Vocal score] Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript vocal score (133 sheets in various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 19, Folder 151)
      Holograph in pencil and ink
    - [White bird. Vocal score. German & English] The White Bird: Opera in One Act / The Poem by Brian Hooker; The Music by Ernest Carter. -- c1924., 1 manuscript vocal score (164 p.), bound; 34 cm. (Box 19; 20, Folder 152-154; 155)
      Holograph, signed, in ink with additions in red ink and pencil
      Negative photocopy without German words, and two positive photocopies with markings (one copy bound) laid in
    - [White bird. Vocal score. German & English] Der weisse Vogel = (The white Bird): Oper in einem Akt / Englischer Text von Brian Hooker; Deutsch von Fritz Remond; Musik von Ernest Carter. -- c1924., 1 manuscript vocal score (132 p.), bound; 33 cm. (Box 20; 21, Folder 156-159; 160-165)
      On cover/title page: Uraufführung in Chicago, 1924. Bühnen-Verlag Trask & Matthias G.m.b.H. Berlin-Charlottenburg, Sesenheimer-Str.27. Alle Rechte vorbehalten! Music copyright 1924 by Ernest Carter. English text copyright 1924 by Yale University Press
      Eleven copies, three unbound, with corrections by Carter and Otto Fessler
      Laid in one copy: Drückfehler im Klavierauszug 'Der weisse Vogel" / E. Carter. -- Rec'd Sept. 2 1928 ([24] p.)
  - Orchestral Works, I.B
    - [Ampersand march; arr.] Ampersand March: für kleines Orchester / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (12 p.) + 34 parts; 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 166)
      Holographs, signed, in pencil and ink
    - [Ampersand march; arr. (Sketches)] Ampersand Marsch: für grosses Orchester / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 36 cm. (Box 22, Folder 166)
      Holograph, signed, in pencil and ink
    - [Andante, orchestra] Andante aus der ersten Suite für Orchester / Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1934 Aug. 24., 1 manuscript score (12 p.); 33 cm. (Box 22, Folder 167)
      Note on title page: 8/24/34 - different from Fessler score, which latter is correct with parts
    - [Andante, orchestra] Andante aus der ersten Suite für Orchester / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (14 p.); 33 cm. (Box 22, Folder 167)
    - [Andante, orchestra] ca. 1934-1938., 45 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 168)
    - [Andante, orchestra], 5 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 169)
      String parts
    - [Andante, orchestra] ca. 1916-1937., 27 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 170)
      Inserts laid in
    - [Andante, orchestra] ca. 1934-1938., 26 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 22, Folder 171)
    - [Honeysuckle waltz; arr.] Honeysuckle Waltz = Geissblatt Walzer / By Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1888 or 1889., 1 manuscript score (34 p.) + 43 parts; 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 172)
      Arr. for orchestra
      Note on first p.: About as arranged by someone for C.W. Stub 1888 or 1889?
    - [Honeysuckle waltz; arr.] Honeysuckle Waltz = Geisblatt [sic] Walzer: für grosses Orchester / von Ernest Carter. -- 1896-1897., 1 manuscript score (44 p.) + 39 parts; 35 cm. (Box 22, Folder 173)
      Holograph, signed, in ink with pencil additions and manuscript (photocopies)
      Score dated 1897 Jun. 4, parts c1896, one part marked "corrected Feb. 16/38"
    - [Honeysuckle waltz; arr.] Waltzes: for Small Orchestra / by Ernest Carter. -- 1910., 1 manuscript score (44 p.) + 23 parts; 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 174)
      Holographs, signed, in ink with red ink additions and manuscript (photocopies)
    - [Honeysuckle waltz; arr.] Honeysuckle Waltz: for Large Orchestra / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (44 p.); 35 cm. (Box 22, Folder 175)
    - [Honeysuckle waltz; arr.] Honeysuckle Waltz = Das Geissblatt: Walzer / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (37 p.); 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 175)
    - [Honeysuckle waltz; arr.] ca. 1896-1910., 80 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 23, Folder 176)
      Holographs and manuscript in ink (in part, photocopies)
    - [Jolly thirds; arr.] The Jolly Thirds / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (15 p.) + 39 parts; 35 cm. (Box 23, Folder 177)
    - [My dainty one; arr.] My dainty "one" = Meine Lieblich / von Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (10 p.) + 27 parts; 34 cm. (Box 23, Folder 178)
    - [My dainty one; arr.] My Dainty One., 1 manuscript score (10 p.); 34 cm. (Box 23, Folder 178)
    - [Princeton festival overture (Sketches)] Princeton Festival Overture: Sketch for Introduction / Ernest Carter. -- 1942 May 17., [1] sheet of music; 17 x 26 cm. (Box 23, Folder 179)
    - [Rague de Pussy; arr.] Rague de Pussy: Franco-American Canned Scales / by Ernest Carter. -- 1916 Jan. 31., 1 manuscript score (15 sheets); 36 cm. (Box 23, Folder 180)
    - [Rague de Pussy; arr.] Rague de Pussy: Franco-American canned scales / by Ernest Carter. -- 1916 Feb.-Mar., 18 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 23, Folder 180)
      Note on folder: 1st set
    - [Rague de Pussy; arr.] Rague de Pussy: Franko-American Canned Scales / by Ernest Carter. -- 1916 Mar. 23-25., 17 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 23, Folder 180)
    - [Sänger im Walde] Sänger im Walde = Springtime in the Woods / von Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (27 p.); 34 cm. (Box 23, Folder 181)
      For orchestra
    - [Sänger im Walde] Charakter Stück: Die Sänger im Walde / von Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([24] p.); 35 cm. (Box 23, Folder 181)
    - [Sänger im Walde] Characterstück [sic]: Die Sänger im Walde / Ernest Carter., 43 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 23, Folder 181)
    - [Scent of the Jessamine] The Scent of the Jessamine. -- [between 1886 and 1888]., 1 manuscript condensed score ([2] p.) + 8 parts; 34 cm. (Box 24, Folder 182)
      Holographs in ink
    - [Scherzo, orchestra] Scherzo / by Ernest Carter. -- 1898-1938., 1 manuscript score (41 p.) + 38 parts; 33 cm. (Box 24, Folder 183)
      Note on title page: copied from parts by Otto Fessler, rec'd Feb. 23/32
    - [Scherzo, orchestra] Scherzo: Score for Small Orchestra. -- ca. 1916-1942., 1 manuscript score (29 p.) + 16 parts; 34 cm. (Box 24, Folder 184)
    - [Scherzo, orchestra] Scherzo / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (26 p.); 36 cm. (Box 24, Folder 185)
    - [Scherzo, orchestra] Scherzo / Ernest Carter., 2 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 24, Folder 186)
      Holograph, signed, and manuscript in ink
      Bassoon and bass parts
    - [Scherzo, orchestra] ca. 1936-1937., 16 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 24, Folder 187)
      Holographs, signed, and manuscript in ink
    - [Scherzo, orchestra], 39 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 24, Folder 188)
    - [Steps song; arr.] Steps Song: Orchestra / Arr. by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.) + 16 parts; 17-35 cm. (Box 24, Folder 189)
      Arr. for string orchestra
    - [Suites, orchestra, D minor (Sketches)] Suite in D moll., [1] sheet of music; 36 cm. (Box 24, Folder 190)
    - [Suites, orchestra, F major (Sketches)] Sketch intro. for I Movement - orchestra Suite in F-major., [1] sheet of music; 34 cm. (Box 24, Folder 191)
      Holograph in pencil
  - Band Works, I.C
    - [Blonde donna. March; arr.] The Blonde Donna March: Act I, Scene 2 NO. 12: Score for Brass Band., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 36 cm. (Box 25, Folder 192)
    - [Blonde donna. March; arr.] The Blonde Donna March / Carter., 17 manuscript parts; 14-19 cm. (Box 25, Folder 192)
      Arr. for brass band
      Envelope with notes laid in
    - [Decennial march; arr.] Decennial March: To fellow classmates of the class of 1888 at Princeton University / By Ernest Carter; Words of class ode (introduced in trio) by T.M. Parrott., 1 manuscript score (8 p.) + 19 parts; 36 cm. (Box 25, Folder 193-196)
      Arr. for band
    - [Steps song; arr.] Steps song / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 25, Folder 197)
    - [Tigers are coming] The Tigers are Coming: Ragtime Bugle March / By Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (11 p.); 33 cm. (Box 25, Folder 198)
      For band
    - [Tigers are coming] The Tigers are Coming: Ragtime Bugle March: Band Score for Cavalry / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (10 p.); 34 cm. (Box 25, Folder 198)
    - [Tigers are coming] The Tigers are Coming: Bugle March: For Military Band and Bugle Corps / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (14 p.); 34 cm. (Box 25, Folder 198)
    - [Tigers are coming] The Tigers are Coming: Bugle March: For Military Band and Bugle Corps / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (12 p.); 35 cm. (Box 25, Folder 198)
    - [Tigers are coming] The Tigers are Coming / by Ernest Carter., 2 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 25, Folder 198)
      Parts for bugles in F
    - [Triple cheer] The Triple Cheer., 24 manuscript parts; 13 x 18 cm. (Box 25, Folder 199)
      Holographs [?] in ink
      Band parts
  - Choral Works, I.D
    - [Abide with me (Sketches)] Abide with me / Ernest Carter. -- 1900 May 15., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 27 cm. (Box 26, Folder 200)
      On back: sketch for "Jesus lover of my soul"
    - [Bright college years] Bright college years: (for male voices) / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by H.S. Durand '81. -- 1923 Mar. 22., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 201)
    - [Bright college years] Bright college years: (For Mixed Voices) or Piano accomp. / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 201)
      Holograph signed, in pencil
    - [Bright college years] Bright college years: (Glee Club Arrangement) / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by H.S. Durand '81., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 201)
    - [Bright college years] Bright College Years: (Glee Club Arrangement) / Music by "Homo"; Words by H.S. Durand., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 33 cm. (Box 26, Folder 201)
    - [Bright college years] Bright College Years / Music by "Homo"; Words by H.S. Durand '81., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 26, Folder 201)
      For chorus (TTBB) and piano
    - [College national hymn] College National Hymn: For Men's voices, organ, and brass / Words by Sidney Lanier; Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([5] p.); 34 cm. (Box 26, Folder 202)
      On title page: Sung by Glee Club + Organ at Princeton's 150th Celebration
    - [College national hymn] College National Hymn: (For mens' voices with organ accompaniment) / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by Sidney Lanier. -- c1896., 1 manuscript part; 27 cm. (Box 26, Folder 202)
      Part for unison voices only
    - [Columbia, Cosmopolis; arr.] Columbia, cosmopolis: (For Male Voices) / Words + Music of verse by "------"; Words + Music of Chorus by "Cosmop.", 1 manuscript close score ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 26, Folder 203)
    - [Columbia, Cosmopolis; arr.] Columbia, Cosmopolis: (Male Voice Arrangement) / Words + Music of verse by "----"; Words + Music of Chorus by "Cosmop.", 1 manuscript close score ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 203)
    - [Columbia! We must win!] Columbia! We Must Win! / Words + Music by "Pigskin." -- 1921., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.) + 2 parts; 26-32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 204)
      Holograph, signed in pencil
      Note on first p.: Spring of 1921 for prize Ernest Carter
    - [Columbia! We must win! Text] Columbia! We must win!: Football Song / Words and music by "Pigskin.", [1] sheet; 28 cm. (Box 26, Folder 204)
      Four other typescript copies laid in
    - [Compline hymn (Sketches)] Compline Hymn., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 13 cm. (Box 26, Folder 205)
    - [Compline hymn. Text] Compline Hymn., [1] sheet; 18 cm. (Box 26, Folder 205)
    - [Decennial march] Decennial March: For Piano and Male-Voices / by Ernest Carter. -- c1898., 1 manuscript vocal score (7 p.); 27 cm. (Box 26, Folder 206)
      Words of class ode (Trio) by T. M. Parrott
    - [Easter hymn (Sketches)] Easter Hymn / E.T.C., [1] sheet of music; 34 cm. (Box 26, Folder 207)
      Unidentified sketch on bottom of page
    - ['88 class ode] '88 Class Ode / [music by] Ernest Carter; [words by] T.M. Parrott., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 24 cm. (Box 26, Folder 208)
    - ['88 class ode] '88 Class Ode / [music by] Ernest Carter; [words by] Thomas M. Parrott., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 24 cm. (Box 26, Folder 208)
      Words on back
    - ['88 reunion song] '88 Reunion Song / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by T.M. Parrott., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.); 26 cm. (Box 26, Folder 209)
      For unison chorus and piano
    - ['88 reunion song] '88 Reunion Song / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by T.M. Parrott., 1 manuscript part; 27 cm. (Box 26, Folder 209)
      For unison chorus
    - [Evening song of Camp Madison] Evening Song of Camp Madison / Words by B.T. Emery., 10 manuscript parts; 28 cm. (Box 26, Folder 210)
      Parts include: tenor I(2), tenor II(3), bass I(3), bass II(2)
      With: Madison Singing Choir, For Madison Square, and Lord Let the Sons
    - [For love's sweet sake] For Love's Sweet Sake / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 27 cm. (Box 26, Folder 211)
      For chorus (TTBB)
      In ink, copied by S.B. Scott
    - [Golden rule] The Golden Rule: (A Round) / Ernest Carter., [1] sheet of music; 24 cm. (Box 26, Folder 211)
    - [Hunting song] Hunting Song and Man in the Moon: for small orchestra. -- 1898 Jan., 1 manuscript score (5 p.) + 12 parts; 27-34 cm. (Box 26, Folder 211)
      For orchestra and male voices (TTBB)
      Note on title page: Written for + played at Herbert's + Mabel's wedding reception at Silver Spring, Jan. 1898 (used some of this in "White Bird" 1917) Words not included in score
      With: Man in the moon
    - [Hurray, hurray, hurray] [1] sheet of music; 13 x 17 cm., Holograph in pencil (Box 26, Folder 211)
    - [Hymns. Selections], 19 manuscript close scores; 27 cm. (Box 26, Folder 212)
      manuscript signed by Carter in ink and pencil
      Arrangements of hymn tunes
      Contents: Austrian hymn -- St. Edith -- Laudes Domini -- Coronation -- St. Gertrude -- St. Leonard -- Nicaea -- Christmas -- St. Marguerite -- Vox Dilecti (two close scores of each except Vox Dilecti)
      Typescript note laid in
    - [I will lift up mine eyes] I Will Lift up Mine Eyes: Psalm 121: For Mixed Voices and Organ / Music by Ernest Carter, 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 213)
      Note on title page: 1st copy; To Arthur Babcock and Choir of the First Congregational Church Redlands, Calif.
      Old envelope dated 1945, in Carter's hand
    - [I will lift up mine eyes] I Will Lift up Mine Eyes: Psalm 121: For Mixed Voices and Organ / Music by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 213)
      Note on title page: 2nd (corrected) copy; To Arthur Babcock and Choir of the First Congregational Church Redlands, Calif.
      Photostat negative laid in
    - [I will lift up mine eyes] Psalm 121: For mixed voices and organ / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript part; 24 cm (Box 26, Folder 213)
      Chorus part
      Two photostats laid in
    - [I will not let Thee go] I will not let Thee go / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 24 x 27 cm. (Box 26, Folder 214)
    - [I will not let Thee go] I Will Not Let Thee Go / Music by Ernest Carter; Words by Rev. J.E. Rankin, D.D. -- Washington, D.C.: Howard University Print, 1895., 1 close score ([1] p.); 22 cm. (Box 26, Folder 214)
      On title page verso: "Amen" in Carter's hand
      Four copies, sketch laid in one copy
    - [I will not let Thee go (Sketches)] I Will Not Let Thee Go., 1 manuscript score ([5] p.); 34 cm. (Box 26, Folder 214)
    - [In heavenly love abiding] In Heavenly Love Abiding: Anthem for Mixed Voices / Music by S. Thalberg and Ernest Carter; Words by Mrs. Waring. -- ca. 1940 Nov., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 215)
      Photostat negative and positives (2 copies) laid in
      Note on one positive photostat: offsets made Nov. 1940
    - [In heavenly love abiding (Sketches)] In Heavenly Love Abiding: Anthem for Mixed Voices / Music by S. Thalberg and Ernest Carter; Words by Mrs. Waring. -- 1940 Sep.- Nov., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 26, Folder 215)
      Note on title page: Draft
    - [In heavenly love abiding (Sketches)] In Heavenly Love Abiding / Music by S. Thalberg and Ernest Carter; Words by Mrs. Waring., 1 manuscript close score ([1] sheet); 24 cm. (Box 26, Folder 215)
    - [In heavenly love abiding] In Heavenly Love Abiding., [1] sheet of music; 24 cm. (Box 26, Folder 215)
      Two copies, words not included
    - [Interesting parallel] An Interesting Parallel., [1] sheet of music; 24 cm. (Box 26, Folder 216)
      "Yale song" and "Anchors A-weigh" to be performed simultaneously